Guide to the Grand Street Publications, Inc. Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Editorial Files, 1982-2004
  - Subseries I.2: Art Files, 1991-2004
    - Issue 66--Secrets, 1998
      - Hiller, Susan (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Meiselas, Susan (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Merewether, Charles (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Migrant Workers (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Nauman, Bruce (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Touch of Evil (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Vyakul, Acharya (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Issue 67--Fire, 1998
      - General (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - Astronomy (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Group Portfolio (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Guo Qiang, Cai (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - King, David (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Klein, Yves (Box 70, Folder 33)
      - Mendieta. Ana (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Murrin, Lou (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Vollmann, Bill (Box 70, Folder 36)
      - Ward, Nari (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Issue 68--Symbols, 1998-1999
      - General (Box 70, Folder 38)
      - Berlin (Box 70, Folder 39)
      - Cole, Willie (Box 70, Folder 40)
      - Corporate Logos (Box 70, Folder 41)
      - Eggleston, William (Box 70, Folder 42)
      - Kafka at the Movies (Box 70, Folder 43)
      - Hammerlein, Chris (Box 70, Folder 44)
      - Jensen, Alfred (Box 70, Folder 45)
      - Luo Brothers (Box 70, Folder 46)
      - Merewether, Charles (Box 70, Folder 47)
      - Ravinder, Reddy (Box 70, Folder 48)
      - Shaker Spirit Drawings (Box 70, Folder 49)
      - Strauss, Levi (Box 70, Folder 50)
      - Tarkovsky, Andre (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Issue 69--Berlin, 1998-1999
      - General, (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 52 to 54)
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 33 to 34)
      - General, (4 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 1 to 4)
      - Ackerman, Franz (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Allamoda, Bettina (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Appelt, Dieter (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Bonvicini, Monica (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Brecht, Bertolt (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Burgen, John (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Dogfilm (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Eichorn, Maria (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Eisenberg, Daniel (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Gabriel, E. Twin (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Haacke, Hans (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Hall, Doug (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - History (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Hoch, Hannah (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Horning, Sabina (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Immendorf, Jorg (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Kahrs, Johannes (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Kienholz, Ed (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Kippenberger, Martin (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Koch, Andreas (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Lewandowski, Via (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Messner, Arwed (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Miller, John (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Penck, A.R. (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Pernice, Manifred (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Rausch, Neo (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Ravensbruk (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Reissberg, Raphael (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Rosenberg, Aura (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Solomoukha, Kristina (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Specker, Heidi (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Stih, Retana (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Westphalen, Olaf (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Issue 70--Against Nature, 2000
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 38 to 39)
      - Beahan Virginia and Laura McPhee (Box 71, Folder 40)
      - Cavalli-Sforza (Box 71, Folder 41)
      - Caven, Ingrid (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - Deen, Georganne, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 43 to 44)
      - Devlin, Lucinda (Box 71, Folder 45)
      - Eliasson, Olafur, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 46 to 47)
      - Found Art (Box 71, Folder 48)
      - Furtwangler, Wilhelm (Box 71, Folder 49)
      - Fuss, Adam (Box 71, Folder 50)
      - Goin, Peter, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 51 to 52)
      - Hesse-Honegger, Cornelia, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Lewandowsky, Via (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Lutter, Vera (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - McPhee, Laura (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Mnouchkine, Ariane (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Nakaya, Fumiko, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Smith, Kiki (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Sugimoto, Hiroshi (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Tambours (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Ziebel, Rob, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 12 to 13)
    - Issue 71--Danger, 2003
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 30 to 31)
      - Atlas Group (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Bareikis, Aidas (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Berman, Wallace (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Burden, Chris (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Celmins, Vija (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Conner, Bruce (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Emerling, Susan and Isabella Kirkland (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Farocki, Harun (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Kalpackjian, Craig (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Kirkland, Isabella (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - L.A. Fine Arts Squad (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Maier, Ati (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Paolozzi (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Rauch, Neo (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Rosenquist, James (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Signer, Roman (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Issue 72--Detours, 2003
      - Bispo do Rosario, Arthur (Box 72, Folder 30)
      - Eggleston, Bill (Box 72, Folder 31)
      - Frank, Robert (Box 72, Folder 32)
      - Jacir, Emily (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Merewether, Charles (Box 72, Folder 34)
      - Mutu, Wangechi (Box 72, Folder 35)
      - Noguchi, Isamu (Box 72, Folder 36)
      - Potrc, Marjetica (Box 72, Folder 37)
      - Sebald (Box 72, Folder 38)
      - Tabucci (Box 72, Folder 39)
      - Tanning, Dorothea (Box 72, Folder 40)
      - Vollman, William (Box 72, Folder 41)
      - Waberi--includes Compact Disc (Box 72, Folder 42)
      - Xingjian, Gao (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Issue 73--Delusions, 2003- 2004
      - General, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Anderson, Walter (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Dali, Salvador (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - DeLillo, Don (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Dittborn, Eugenio (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Dube, Anita (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Ensor, James (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Las Posas (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Mann, Sally (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Matta, Roberto (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Michaux, Henri (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Theophile, Bra (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Wearing, Gillian (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Subseries I.3: Author Files, 1989-2004
    Literary Materials from the 1990s on were arranged alphabetically by author rather than chronologically by issue and this subseries retains this original order as well as its division into two sections: poetry and prose. The folder for each author only represents the author's work published in Grand Street in the 1990s. Some writers also had published work in the magazine in the 1980s and these materials can be found in Subseries I.1, arranged chronologically by issue.
    - Poetry
      - Adonis--also known as Ali Ahmad Said, 1996, Undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Agren, Gosta, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Alexander, Meena, 1991-1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Ali, Agha Shalid, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Allen, Fergus, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Amen, Grover, 1991-2004 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Amichai, Yehuda, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Amirthonayagam, Indron, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Ammons, A.R, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Apollinaire, Guillaume, Undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Armantrout, Ray, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Armitage, Simon, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Artaud, Antoin, 1994-1997 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Ashbury, John, 1994-1997 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Avianus, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Baca, Jimmy Santiago, Undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Bamforth, Iain, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Baraka, Amiri, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Barr, Burlin, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Beasley, Bruce, 2001-2003 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Belieu, Erin, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Bellen, Martine, 1992-1995 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Bellows, Nathaniel, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Beyer, Lynne Undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Bierman, Wolf 1998 (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Blau Du Plessis, Rachel 1990 (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - Boggis, Jay, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - Borges, Jorge Luis, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - Braun, Volker, 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - Brecht, Bertolt, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Cahill, Christopher, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Cameron, Juen, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Carlson, Michael, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Celaya, Gabriel, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Cesaire, Aime, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - Chouliaras, Yiorgos, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Christensen, Inger, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Christopher, Nicholas, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 39)
      - Clark, Jeff, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 40)
      - Coolidge, Clark, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Corbett, Bill, 1996-1998, (2 Folders) (Box 48, Folder 42 to 43)
      - Cornish, Sam, Undated (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - Creeley, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Cruz, Cynthia, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Csoori, Sandor,, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 47)
      - Darwish, Mahmood, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      - Dao, Bei, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 49)
      - Dauer, Casey, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 50)
      - Deane, Seamus, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 51)
      - Deanovitch, Connie, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 52)
      - Debeljak, Ales, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 53)
      - Dewdney, Christopher, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 54)
      - Diaz, Joanne, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 55)
      - DiPalma, Ray, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 56)
      - Dove, Richard, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 57)
      - Dragomoshenko, Arkadii, 1991-1995 (Box 48, Folder 58)
      - Drummond De Andrade, Carlos, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 59)
      - Edmunds, Martin, Undated (Box 48, Folder 60)
      - Egyptian Love Poems, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - Ellis, Thomas Sayers, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - Ellis, Thomas Sayers, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 61)
      - Equi, Elaine, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 62)
      - Eshleman, Clayton, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 63)
      - Farley, Paul, Undated (Box 48, Folder 64)
      - Farmer, Wayne, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 65)
      - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Fisher, Alexander, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Fitterman, Rob, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Forrest, Gander, 1996-1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Fulton, Lee, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Gardinier, Suzanne, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Gergely, Agnes, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Gilbert, Celia, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Gizzi, Peter, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Gladding, Jody, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Gorham, Sarah, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Graf, Dieter, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Graham, Jorie, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Graham, Taylor, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Greenlaw, Lavinia, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Grennan, Eamon, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Grubein, Durs, 1999-2003 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Guillen, Jorge, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Haining, James, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - HaNagid, Shmuel, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Harjo, Joy, Undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Harwood, Lee, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Hejinian, Lyn, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Helder, Herberto, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Hellman, David, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Henry, Brian, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Herbeck, Ernst, 1992-2002 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - Herbert, Zginiew, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Herondas, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - Hertmans, Stefan, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Hoffman, Michael, 1996-2004 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Hoffman, Roald, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Hollander, John, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Holub, Miroslav, 1991-1994 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Howe, Fanny, 1994-1996 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Hunt, Laird, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Ignatow, David, Undated (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Inkala, Jouai, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - Jackson, Major, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Jacobson, Josephine, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - Jarnagin, Willa, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 40)
      - Jarnot, Lisa, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 41)
      - Jasper, Matt, 1995, (2 Folders) (Box 49, Folder 42 to 43)
      - Johnson, Stacey Land, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - Jones, Rodney, 1990-1995 (Box 49, Folder 45)
      - Kahf, Mohja, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      - Kapoor, Suman K., 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 47)
      - Kelly, Robert, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      - Kinsella, John, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      - Kipp, Karen, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 50)
      - Kirchwey, Karl, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      - Kirsch, Sarah, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 52)
      - Kisang Poetry, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Kleinzahler, August, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 53)
      - Kocbek, Edward, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      - Koch, Kenneth, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 55)
      - Kondis, Yannis, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 56)
      - Kruger, Michael, 1992-2003 (Box 49, Folder 57)
      - Krakowski, Damon, 1992-2002 (Box 49, Folder 58)
      - K’uan, Fan, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 59)
      - Kunert, Gunter, 1999-2004 (Box 49, Folder 60)
      - Landau, Deborah, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 61)
      - Larsen, Lance, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 62)
      - Larsson, Stig, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 63)
      - Lasdun, James, 1999-2002 (Box 49, Folder 64)
      - Laughlin, James, 1992-1997 (Box 49, Folder 65)
      - Lawrence, Nick, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 66)
      - Lease, Joseph, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 67)
      - Lee, Li-Young, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 68)
      - Lefevre, Adam, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 69)
      - Lenier, Sue, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 70)
      - Lezama Lima, Jose, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 71)
      - Lihn, Enrique, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 72)
      - Liu, Timothy, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 73)
      - Longley, Michael, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 74)
      - Lukas, Brennen T., 1998 (Box 49, Folder 75)
      - Mackey, Nathaniel, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 76)
      - Malanga, Gerard, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 77)
      - Malaparte Poems, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Mamet, David, Undated (Box 49, Folder 78)
      - Manrique, Jaime, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 79)
      - Martial, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 80)
      - Martin, Herbert Woodward, 1989- 1991 (Box 49, Folder 81)
      - Matur, Bejan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 82)
      - Mayer, Bernadette, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 83)
      - Mayrocker, Friederike, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 84)
      - McCain, Gillian, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 85)
      - McClure, Michael, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 86)
      - McCord, Andrew, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 87)
      - McDonald, Walter, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 88)
      - Mee, Susie, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 89)
      - Melo neto, Joao Cabral de, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 90)
      - Merwin, W.S., 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Middleton, Christopher, 1994-1997 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Mistral, Gabriela, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Mlinko, Ange, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Mobilio, Albert, Undated, circa 1990s- 2000s (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Mootoo, Shani, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Montague, John, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Montale, Eugenio, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Morelli, Jenny, Undated, circa 1990s- 2000s (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Morley, Hilda, 1993-1997 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Moten, Fred, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Müller, Heiner, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Müller, Inge, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Murray, Les, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Nalley, Richard, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Nasrin, Tashima, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Notley, Alice, Undated, circa 1990s- 2000s (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Nurkse, Dennis, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - O’Brien, Michael, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Olds, Sharon, Undated, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Oleschinski, Brigitte, 1999-2004 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Oppenheim, Meret, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - O’Reilly, Caitriona, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Ormsby, Eric, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Oravecz, Imre, 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Oren, Aras, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Oswald, Alice, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Ovid, Undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Palmer, Michael, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Paulin, Tom, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Pankey, Eric, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Pastior, Oskar, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Paz, Octavio, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - Pessoa, Fernando, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Pizarnik, Alejandra, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Porche, Verandah, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Potokar, Jure, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Ray, David, Undated (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - Reddy, Srikanth, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Redgrove, Peter, 1992-1995 (Box 50, Folder 39)
      - Reid, Christopher, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 40)
      - Rhett, Kathryn, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Roberts, Michael Symmons, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Robertson, Robin, 1995-2003 (Box 50, Folder 43)
      - Robinson, Kit, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Rodefer, Stephen, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 45)
      - Rosen, Kenneth, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 46)
      - Rudman, Mark, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 47)
      - Rosselli, Amelia, Undated (Box 50, Folder 48)
      - Sacks, Peter, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 49)
      - Saenz, Alicia Vogel, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 50)
      - Salamun, Tomaz, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Sartorius, Joachim, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Scattergood, Amy, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 53)
      - Schaller, Sharon M., 1999 (Box 50, Folder 54)
      - Schelling, Andrew, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 55)
      - Schiff, Jeff, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 56)
      - Schjerven, Torgeir, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 57)
      - Schneiderman, Jason, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 58)
      - Schultz, Phil, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 59)
      - Sereni, Vittorio, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 60)
      - Scherbina, Tatiana, Undated (Box 50, Folder 61)
      - Shepherd, Reginald, 1994-1997 (Box 50, Folder 62)
      - Shurin, Aaron, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 63)
      - Sikelianos, Eleni, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 64)
      - Simic, Charles, 1990-1998 (Box 50, Folder 65)
      - Sisson, C. H., 1993 (Box 50, Folder 66)
      - Smith, Bruce, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 67)
      - Smith, Charlie, 1996-2004 (Box 50, Folder 68)
      - Soldofsky, Alan, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 69)
      - Sonnevi, Goran, 1998 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Snyder, Gary, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 70)
      - Sorescu, Marin, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 71)
      - Starbuck, George, 1988-1990 (Box 50, Folder 72)
      - Steinberg, Hugh, 1990-1994 (Box 50, Folder 73)
      - Strickland, Stephanie, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 74)
      - Sweeney, Matthew, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 75)
      - Swenson, Cole, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 76)
      - Swoboda, Terese, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 77)
      - Synessio, Anastasia, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 78)
      - Szporluk, Larissa, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 79)
      - Tarn, Nathaniel, Undated (Box 50, Folder 80)
      - Tate, James, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 81)
      - Thomsen, Soren Ulrik, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 82)
      - Tranter, John, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 83)
      - Uchida, Kyoko, 2000-2003 (Box 50, Folder 84)
      - Ungaretti, Giuseppi, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 85)
      - Vaeth, Kim, Undated (Box 50, Folder 86)
      - Vallejo, Cesar, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 87)
      - Van Cleave, Ryan G, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 88)
      - Vanderholen, Robert, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 89)
      - Van Winckel, Nance, Undated (Box 50, Folder 90)
      - Villaurrutia, Xavier, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 91)
      - Waldrop, Rosmarie, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 92)
      - Warren, Rosanna, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 93)
      - Wasserman, Jo Ann, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 94)
      - Weiss, Mark, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 95)
      - Welish, Marjorie, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 96)
      - Whalen, John, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Wicks, Susan, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 97)
      - Williams, John Hartley, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 98)
      - Wilson, Fiona, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Winman, Christian, Undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Wolff, Rebecca, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Wright, Charles, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Yasusada, Araki, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Yau, John, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Yilmaz, Levent, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Young, Brian, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Young, Kevin, 1996-1998 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Yurkievich, Saul, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Zenith, Richard, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Prose
      - Abdolah, Kader, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Abreu, Caio Fernando, Undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Ackerman, Diane, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Adorno, Theodor W., 1991-1995 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Aji, Aron, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Alcalay, Ammiel, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Alexis, Andre, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Agustin, Jose, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Al-Radi, Nuha, 1997-2003 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Als, Hilton, 1994-1997, (2 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 20 to 21)
      - Alsadin, Nuan, Undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Althaus, Keith, Undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Althusser, Louis, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Am, Nguyen Thi, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Amen, Grover, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Ancient Egyptian Love Lyrics, Undated (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Anders, Daniel Lee, 1996-2004 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Anderson, Olie, 1989-1995 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Anger, Kenneth, Undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - Antunes, Antonio, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Antunes, Lobo, 1996-1998 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Arenas, Reinaldo, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Arredondo, Ines, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 34)
      - Arzola, Jorge Luis, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Auster, Paul, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Azua, Felix de, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - Bachmann, Ingeborg, Undated (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - Barcelona, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - Baker, Alison, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 39)
      - Basara, Svetislav, 199 (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Bauchau, Henry, 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 40)
      - Bataille, Georges, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 41)
      - Bates, Randy, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 42)
      - Beckett, Samuel, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 43)
      - Bell, Charles, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 44)
      - Benjamin, Walter, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 45)
      - Berlo, Janet, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 46)
      - Berberova, Nina, 1991-1995, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Bergman, Ingmar, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Berlin, Brigid, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Berlin, 1999, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Beyer, Marcel, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Biermann, Wolf, Undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Bioy Casares, Adolfo (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Birov, Andrei, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Bogen, Dan, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Boland, Eavan, Undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Bolaño, Roberto, 1998-2003, (2 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Boll, Heinrich, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Borgmann, Kendra, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Borges, Jorge Luis, 1993-1996 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Botsford, Keith, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Boudjedra, Rachid, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Boulez, Pierre, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Bourdieu, Pierre, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Bourgeois, Louise, Undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Bowles, Paul, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Braun, Volker, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Brecht, Bertolt, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 26)